One of the good things about whatever
your first draft is is that you've
actually done this at all, right?
So you've actually you've actually
written something you've bothered to start
I read an article by somebody who had
decided he wanted to be a writer and
he went about it in a very
interesting way in that
he contacted the publisher
and Rather than saying oh, here's my book.
He said can you Send me all
of the books that you've been
sent over the last year I
volunteered to read your slush pile.
is what it's called And he said one
of the things that he
found really interesting
about that. He read a hundred books
in a year is That a lot of them
even they might be in the right
length But they were unfinished They
they were kind of you know, they
they weren't they were
half-arsed or they were
like Seven eighths asked or whatever,
but they weren't finished Somebody
hadn't put all of the effort into into
them that they needed to be put into them
to make them feel that they were finished